[Home](https://smihub.io/) > Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Oct 11, 2022

Collection of Personal Information
----------------------------------

We keep track of your IP address and the dates and times you access smihub.online only to analyze patterns, run the site smoothly, understand how users move on our website, and collect broad demographic information for internal use. Rest assured that none of this data is linked to your personally identifiable information whatsoever.

**Links to third-party Websites**

We have provided links to other websites for your convenience, but please note that we cannot vouch for the privacy policies of these sites. It is likely that they have different rules about collecting and using your data, so be sure to read their policies carefully before providing any information.

Your Privacy
------------

Your privacy is important to us, and we want to be clear about the data we collect and how it is used. This notice explains our information practices. You can find this notice on our homepage or any page where personal information may be requested.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
----------------------------------------------

Google, our advertising vendor, uses cookies to show you ads based on your visits to this site and other sites. This allows them to serve targeted advertisements that may be of interest to you.

If you want to stop Google from tracking your activity, visit their ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). User tracking is controlled by Google’s own privacy policies.

Not only may the smihub.online website use cookies to analyze visitors’ activities on the site, but they may also do so in order to assess advertising effectiveness and for other reasons that will be outlined in their own privacy policies. However, smihub.online has no access or control over these cookies used by third-party advertisers.

Changes to this Privacy Statement
---------------------------------

We may update this privacy policy at any time, so please check back often. If you have questions about our privacy policy, feel free to contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://smihub.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
